<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kongesalen 1-4 on Booster Conference 2024 Bergen</title>
    <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kongesalen 1-4 on Booster Conference 2024 Bergen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Experiences from LIVE TV shows at NRK</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/experiences-from-live-tv-shows-at-nrk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/experiences-from-live-tv-shows-at-nrk/</guid>
      <description>When the host of a TV-show tells a million viewers to go to our web app on saturday evenings, we get quite a lot of traffic in a very small amount of time. What have we learned from creating systems that are broadcast critical for approx. 10 minutes every Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hero to Zero and back again...</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/from-hero-to-zero-and-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/from-hero-to-zero-and-back-again/</guid>
      <description>In the winter of 2022 I went on maternity leave. Little did I know what awaited me six months later when I tried to get back into the swing of things.
I had once been a go-to person in my team, confidently making architectural decisions. Now, I found myself repeatedly asking the same questions about Spring Boot.
This is my story of how it felt like going back to work, with a brain that was suddenly failing me, and the way back towards normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakten på data </title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/jakten-p%C3%A5-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/program/wednesday/9_short_talks_and_workshops/kongesalen_1_4/jakten-p%C3%A5-data/</guid>
      <description>I 2020 ble en utvikler dømt i Bergen tingrett for datainnbrudd etter at han hadde benyttet seg av et API hos Statens Vegvesen for å laste ned offentlig data. Dette er en sak som fortsatt sitter friskt i minne for mange, og som datajournalist tenker jeg på den hver gang jeg oppsøker offentlig data.
Utvikleren anket og ble til slutt frikjent, men hva hadde skjedd om han hadde brukt de samme metodene for datainnsamling som norsk presse benytter seg av daglig?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
