<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on Booster Conference 2022 Bergen</title>
    <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on Booster Conference 2022 Bergen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:40:13 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anders-nor%C3%A5s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anders-nor%C3%A5s/</guid>
      <description>Originally educated in arts and design, Anders has spent quarter of a century writing code.
He has given numerous talks and keynotes at conferences such as JavaZone, NDC, J-Fall, Øredev and many more. Have given 100+ conference talks to a variety of audiences including media, design and hardcore computer science. Known for an energetic and highly engaging presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/andr%C3%A9-berge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/andr%C3%A9-berge/</guid>
      <description> Masters degree in Algorithms from UiB Been working as a software developer for about 1.5 years. Currently working at Kraftlauget. Mainly been working with React, as well as some Angular and C#  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anette-bergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anette-bergo/</guid>
      <description>Anette har lang fartstid i IT-bransjen og har holdt en rekke foredrag og workshops på Booster før - men har nå tatt en høyresving i karrieren og kommer denne gangen med noe helt annet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-landro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-landro/</guid>
      <description>Anne er tjeneste- og UX-designer i Experis. Hun er levende opptatt av å finne de gode løsningene på brukernes reelle behov</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/areti-panou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/areti-panou/</guid>
      <description>I am a Product Owner at SAP SE, working on internal tools that help developers do their job more easily. I like finding out what the big picture is and how to bring the right people together to improve it. I blog my questions on software development at: https://unremarkabletester.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/bj%C3%B8rn-einar-bjartnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/bj%C3%B8rn-einar-bjartnes/</guid>
      <description>.NET developer and architect with a keen interest in Domain Driven Design and Lean principles. Currently working in 4Subsea with https://4insight.io/. Worked six years in the exciting streaming market for NRK, Norway&amp;rsquo;s public broadcaster. I have a background from the oil &amp;amp; gas industry and spent my first year after university on drilling rigs and several years after that on production facilities working with distributed process control systems.
My main interests are best summed up from my latest blog posts https://nrkbeta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie-haugstvedt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie-haugstvedt/</guid>
      <description>Cecilie is an accessibility enthusiast working as a test consultant. She loves working in agile teams, is a proponent of automating all manual processes, and has a special interest in making applications accessible for all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie_wian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie_wian/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor i Educational Psychology, Master in Digital Culture. Cecilie has a big heart for users, as well as the tech we interact with. At Bouvet she works with testing and security. As a experienced tester Cecilie is all about testing what matters, and making tech safe for human use. You can find her on linkedin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-sloper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-sloper/</guid>
      <description>Name: Christian Sloper Position: Partner and Data scientist group leader for data science at Sonat Consulting Bergen.
Background: PhD in algorithms and complexity theory 15 years work experience as a database and BI specialist, data scientist and python developer.
I gave a talk at Booster 2019: https://2019.boosterconf.no/talks/1300</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christoffer-vig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christoffer-vig/</guid>
      <description>Ancient Philosopher, turned coder right before the dot-com bubble burst. Worked in various environments, lately much into DevOps and agile transformations, micro services with Java in Kubernetes and Jenkins X.
Working at CoWork</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/daan-van-berkel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/daan-van-berkel/</guid>
      <description>Daan van Berkel is a enthusiastic software tinkerer with a knack for presenting technical details in a clear and concise manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/david-mellum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/david-mellum/</guid>
      <description>David is a developer and agile coach at Frende Forsikring with a love for obvious and precise problem solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/elizabeth-zagroba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/elizabeth-zagroba/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth is Quality Lead at Mendix in Rotterdam. She reviews and contributes code to a Python test automation repository for 15+ teams building Mendix apps across three units. She builds exploratory testing skills by asking pointed questions throughout the unit, facilitating workshops, and coordinating an ensemble (mob) testing practice. She injects what she learns from conferences, books, and meetups into her daily work, and spreads her knowledge through the company-wide Agile guild she facilitates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/embla-flatlandsmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/embla-flatlandsmo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Embla! My main hustle is being a robotics student at NTNU, but I really enjoy making music videos and digital illustrations! When not at school, I&amp;rsquo;m normally tinkering on some art or coding project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/erik-assum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/erik-assum/</guid>
      <description>Erik works as a clojure programmer at Ardoq, a Norwegian startup in the EA-space. He’s a mainly a backend programmer, but tends to work wherever the code is bad enough. Given time he’ll eventually drift into some sort of devops role while trying to figure out how to run the current project even better.
Lately, he&amp;rsquo;s been lurking around open-source Clojure projects looking for easy bugs to fix. This is his way of paying back to the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/filip-van-laenen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/filip-van-laenen/</guid>
      <description>Filip van Laenen started his career at Computas in the previous millennium, first as a Java developer, later as a business analyst, IT architect, and various other project roles. He&amp;rsquo;s guilty of lots of bad drawings, but tries to improve himself, and would like to make the world a better place by helping others to improve too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henriette-stokholm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henriette-stokholm/</guid>
      <description>I am a consultant at Rainfall. I like users, exploring unknown areas, and doing things differently. Also, I like things making sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henrik-gundersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henrik-gundersen/</guid>
      <description>Henrik is a really lazy developer (hence all the automation focus!) working as a solutions architect at Sparebanken Vest in Bergen. When he is not working on the security software at SPV, Henrik takes his kayak for a spin or runs around a track really slowly. He is passionate about sharing tips &amp;amp; tricks and lessons learned so that others can (more) safely navigate the dangerous waters of tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henrik-walker-moe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/henrik-walker-moe/</guid>
      <description>Henrik jobber i Bekk som temaeier for Sikkerhet og har over 15 års erfaring i bransjen. Når han finner noe han brenner for å dele med bransjen så kommer det gjerne i form av innlegg på en blogg, i sosiale medier eller fra talerstolen på konferanser. Henrik er også styremedlem i NNUG og arrangerer Meetups for det norske utviklersamfunnet, bl.a. den årlige Microsoft Azure Bootcamp i Oslo.
Faglig fokus de siste årene har vært på IT-sikkerhet og Open Source, hvor Henrik bruker fritiden på å bl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ina-aschim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ina-aschim/</guid>
      <description>Ina er en UX-designer som er opptatt av at vi ikke må glemme brukerne som har dårligst digitale forutsetninger.
Hun har tidligere jobbet med digitale løsninger relatert til sosialhjelp og kommunale boliger. Da ble hun kjent med ikke bare vanskeligstilte brukerne i belastende livssituasjoner, men også ansatte som gir mye av seg selv for å ivareta disse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jan-erik-rediger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jan-erik-rediger/</guid>
      <description>Jan-Erik works at Mozilla, organizes RustFest and loves to enable people to share knowledge and expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jan-strandbakke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jan-strandbakke/</guid>
      <description>Head of development at Tripletex. With many years from the software industry Jan now leads the development department at Tripletex. He believes in trust-based leadership and has focus on building great teams with great speed making a fantastic product.
https://www.linkedin.com/in/jstrandbakke/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jimmy-byrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jimmy-byrum/</guid>
      <description>I really just like building things- websites, APIs, teams, whatever is needed. I&amp;rsquo;ve been lucky enough to stumble into a career in tech, and am currently working as an engineering manager in Vipps. I started out in 2000 just before the dot-com crash, learned how to properly code somewhere along the way, worked with some big companies that needed scale and cool startups that needed a bit of everything. These days I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying the good life in Norway, hopefully speaking passable Norwegian, and enjoying brown cheese sandwiches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/johannes-brodwall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/johannes-brodwall/</guid>
      <description>Johannes Brodwall works as principal software engineer for Sopra Steria. By day he builds software that on a good day helps save lives. In the evenings he likes to dive deep into the details of the technology underlying secured software. Even though TLS and HTTPS is universally used it is poorly understood. Johannes hopes to change this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/johannes-harestad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/johannes-harestad/</guid>
      <description>Johannes Harestad jobber som utvikler i Kantega og elsker å programmere smarte løsninger med god UX. Det er sjelden nyttig med smarte løsninger på feil problem, og derfor er han alltid ivrig på å samarbeide tett med design- og produktfolk for å forstå sluttbrukeren sitt behov. Han har vært med på å skape løsninger med magisk brukeropplevelse i bedrifter som Fiskeridirektoratet, Flytoget og Vipps. På fritiden maler han små plastfigurer for å gjenskape legendariske fantasikamper mellom alver og orker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/john-christian-l%C3%B8nningdal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/john-christian-l%C3%B8nningdal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kasia-szulc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kasia-szulc/</guid>
      <description>Trained archaeologist who nowadays specializes in discovering history of applications. Always eager to learn secrets of legacy products. Kasia is currently a Product Manager at Dynatrace, where she helping build perfect tools for Log Monitoring. Wherever Kasia can get involved in quality and testing you will see her there. Always looking to learn something new everyday. Improves to help others as speaker and trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kevin-baum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kevin-baum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kim-nena-duggen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kim-nena-duggen/</guid>
      <description>As an organizational architect in the field of new work, self-organization and (IT) strategy, Kim Duggen is in her element when she works with people who want to do something themselves instead of making do with theory or sample solutions. Depending on the situation, she switches to the role of consultant, coach or trainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/knut-tveitane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/knut-tveitane/</guid>
      <description>MSc in Software Development from IT-University of Copenhagen
Many years experience (too many?) as independent consultant, and later as senior systems developer for Delfi Data and the Norwegian Institute of Public Health
Knows several languages more or less fluently: Cobol, Italian, Danish, Delphi, SQL, English, Java&amp;hellip; Native languages are C# and Norwegian
Currently slightly retired but still doing a lot of things that I find interesting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristine-br%C3%A5dland-kjellsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristine-br%C3%A5dland-kjellsen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lars-hopland-nest%C3%A5s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lars-hopland-nest%C3%A5s/</guid>
      <description>Lars is Sr. Engineering Manager in Sbanken by day and developer by night. He has a master’s degree in secure and reliable communication from the University of Bergen, and has worked as software developer, penetration tester and security architect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lena-wiberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lena-wiberg/</guid>
      <description>Lena is the author/creator of “Would Heu-risk it?” - a book and a card deck around risk and software testing. She is also Engineering Manager at Mentimeter, where she works on growing people and scaling the engineering organisation. Using her long background in development and testing as a base, she now uses her skills on scaling others rather than software. She believes continuous improvement is something we should all strive for by keeping up to date and always challenge ourselves, our assumptions and the way things are done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lovise-justad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/lovise-justad/</guid>
      <description>Lovise er produkteier for selvbetjeningsløsninger for økonomisk sosialhjelp i NAV. Hun er utdannet sosionom, og har jobbet med mange forskjellige brukergrupper.
Lovise har erfaring med å bygge relasjoner med de sårbare brukerne, og er opptatt av å inkludere brukerne under utformingen av digitale tjenester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mads-lundeland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mads-lundeland/</guid>
      <description>Software developer at TV 2 with experience of running applications with Kafka Streams and Elasticsearch in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mads-opheim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mads-opheim/</guid>
      <description>Software engineer who wants to make people awesome in a safe environment. Test-driven development, Domain-driven design and Modern agile are favourite techniques. Working as tech lead in Computas, currently on a project for the Norwegian Tax Authorities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/malin-c-karlsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/malin-c-karlsen/</guid>
      <description>Malin C. Karlsen is a senior advisor in Variant. With a degree in management, project management and marketing and extensive experience from a wide range of projects, Malin has an extra commitment to building bridges between different disciplines and different people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marija-slavkovik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marija-slavkovik/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marius-krakeli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marius-krakeli/</guid>
      <description>Marius is a programmer with a fondness for fantastic user experiences. He is fascinated by all aspects of JavaScript and is both producer and panelist on the JavaScript podcast “BartJS Podcast”. When he’s not working as a consultant at Variant, and need a break from programming, he is very entertained by video games and video production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marte-%C3%B8vre%C3%A5s-thuen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/marte-%C3%B8vre%C3%A5s-thuen/</guid>
      <description>Jeg har mastergrad i fysikk og doktorgrad i medisinsk teknologi fra NTNU, og 10 års erfaring fra det kommersielle innovasjonsfirmaet NordicNeuroLab, som leverer medisinsk utstyr og programvare. Der jobbet jeg som teknologisjef, med spesielt ansvar for utvikling av dataprogram for medisinsk bildeanalyse. Siden januar 2021 har jeg vært ansatt som teamleder ved Seksjon for Utvikling i Helse Vest IKT, og produktkoordinator for Sensortjenesten. Seksjon for Utvikling ved Helse Vest IKT har over 40 utviklere og integrasjonsarkitekter, og jobber med utvikling av ulike typer software løsninger for helseforetakene i Helse Vest, med mål om å forbedre og forenkle arbeidshverdagen, og å ta i bruk ny teknologi for mer effektiv og smartere sykehusdrift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-b%C3%A5rnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-b%C3%A5rnes/</guid>
      <description>På papiret er Martin en utvikler hos Kantega, men interessen for kundene og for å lage løsninger som skaper verdi har gradvis ført han over i roller som handler mer om design og prosessledelse. Han snakker like godt IT som han snakker design, og er opptatt av at gode løsninger skapes sammen i felleskap på tvers av faglige bakgrunner og roller. Han er også opptatt av hvordan målstyring kan bidra til å skape automoni hos team og slår gjerne av en prat om når en kan, og ikke minst når en ikke kan, bruke OKR ol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-gundersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-gundersen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-strand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-strand/</guid>
      <description>Martin har siden 2018 forsket på kryptografi ved Forsvarets forskningsinstitutt, og har de siste årene primært jobbet med kvantesikker kryptografi for ubevoktede enheter. Før det tok han utdanning innen matematikk og kryptologi ved NTNU, noe som kulminerte i en doktorgrad om e-valg og homomorf kryptering.
Programmeringsmessig trådde Martin sine barnsben i Turbo Pascal 5.5, lærte Delphi 4 med hjelp av bøker fra det daværende høgskolebiblioteket i Bodø, men nøyer seg i dag stort sett med pragmatisk bruk av Python til de daglige behovene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-valen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-valen/</guid>
      <description>Martin is a fullstack developer working at Kantega who likes to explain the simple and less simple concepts he has learnt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/may-britt-haugsv%C3%A6r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/may-britt-haugsv%C3%A6r/</guid>
      <description>Engineering manager and #vennligrebell, Sbanken She has a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Software Engineering from Sunderland University and has worked as a fullstack developer for over 18 years. Started as an engineering manager in May and have a strong passion for teams deciding their own workflow and processes. Each team is different and no size fits all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mikael-brevik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mikael-brevik/</guid>
      <description>Mikael Brevik har lang erfaring som utvikler og foredragsholder i store nasjonale og internasjonale konferanser. Mikael har 2 programmeringspodcaster på Norsk og arrangerer Trondheims JavaScript-meetup og jobber til det daglige som Variants Chief Community Officer. Mikael er opptatt av kommunikasjon, teams og programmeringsspråk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-nygaard-%C3%A5snes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-nygaard-%C3%A5snes/</guid>
      <description>Morten Nygaard Åsnes works at Dfind Consulting as a senior consultant. His current assignment is with KS - Digitale Fellestjenester, where he&amp;rsquo;s working with Java and Kotlin. He&amp;rsquo;s previously given presentations and held workshops at javaBin on Kotlin and other topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mufrid-krilic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/mufrid-krilic/</guid>
      <description>Domain-Driven Design Coach at CoWork, a consultancy traveling together with the customers on their IT-transformation journey.
Experienced software architect, developer and coach, with background from telecom and healthcare, thus being deeply involved in developing enterprise-solutions in complex domains. As a leader and coach for several development teams, Mufrid has been tireless on knowledge sharing in the organization and increasing co-developer’s business understanding. His professional philosophy is rooted in Domain-Driven Design and in building agile and technical coaching culture on an organization-wide level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nadia-tokerud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nadia-tokerud/</guid>
      <description>Nadia er en designer som liker å finne unnskyldninger for å få jobbe sammen med flere fagfelt. Hvorfor? Fordi god inspirasjon kommer fra alle andre steder enn hennes eget hode. Dessuten mener hun at det mest spennende i verden er å lære noe nytt. Noe hun gjør stort sett hver dag fra både brukere og kollegaer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nicolai-gjellestad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nicolai-gjellestad/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Nicolai, a 32 year old dad, partner and developer. After working for different employers since 2014 I&amp;rsquo;m now self employed in Nicode. I like writing code in Go! Check out my website at nicode.dev og my Github account https://github.com/nicolaigj</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nikolai-norman-andersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nikolai-norman-andersen/</guid>
      <description>Nikolai works as a developer in public healthcare with high demands for privacy. He has worked as the DPO in a startup that delivers software to doctors in Norway, Danmark and Germany. He is has the CIPP/E and CIPPM certifications from IAPP. Nikolai is a consultant at Variant in Oslo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nils-norman-hauk%C3%A5s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/nils-norman-hauk%C3%A5s/</guid>
      <description>I work as the CTO of Netlife Bergen where I delete code, cultivate a safe space for technical excellence and research new ways to have less meetings. Happy to chat about legacy code, ethical source, open source and the IndieWeb movement.
My personal web site: https://nilsnh.no My previous talks: https://nilsnh.no/page/talks/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/olav-loen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/olav-loen/</guid>
      <description>Olav er en utvikler som foretrekker å være utleid som prosjektleder, slik at han kan kode egne prosjekter på fritiden. I det siste har Sbankens API fanget hans interesse og erfaringene har ledet til dette kodeverkstedet. Tidligere har han har vært gjesteforeleser hos Høgskolen på Vestlandet (HVL) i moderne systemutviklingsmetoder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/oliver-zeigermann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/oliver-zeigermann/</guid>
      <description>Oliver is a software developer from Hamburg, Germany and has been a practitioner for more than 3 decades. He specializes in frontend development and machine learning. He is the author of multiple video courses and textbooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/patrick-monslaup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/patrick-monslaup/</guid>
      <description>Patrick Monslaup is a technical manager (fagleder), team lead and full-stack developer in Knowit Experience Bergen. As a technical manager he works on facilitating professional development, onboarding, and collaboration in general. He is especially interested in improving how we work together, often focusing on soft skills, team dynamics, process and code quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/peter-bull-hove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/peter-bull-hove/</guid>
      <description>Peter Bull Hove is a developer and tech lead at Bouvet ASA, currently leading the development of a cloud solution for digitalization of the Norwegian ocean industries. Originally from Bergen, he graduated from NTNU with a Masters Degree in Cybernetics and Robotics with a with specializations within AI, sensor technology and data processing. Peter is passionate about cooperation between people and organizations, and how one can, through cooperation, find new solutions that push the current boundaries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricco-f%C3%B8rgaard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricco-f%C3%B8rgaard/</guid>
      <description>Ricco is an avid backend developer from Apparat AS in Bergen. He has more than 15 years of experience from various industries such as telecom, social sciences, and video streaming. The last few years his focus has been mostly on Go, event driven architechtures, and Kubernetes.
In his spare time Ricco enjoys playing the guitar, growing stuff, cooking stuff, and tinkering with all kinds of IoT and home automation. He runs his own LoRa WAN gateway and a flight tracker that feeds flight data to many different trackers, including Flightradar24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricki-sickenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricki-sickenger/</guid>
      <description>Programmer, gamer, father of three kids. Games, Backend, Frontend, AR/VR and IT Consultant. Also a hobby game developer and retro computer enthusiast. =)
Ricki blogs at http://sickenger.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rune-reisegg-jacobsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rune-reisegg-jacobsen/</guid>
      <description>Rune has worked the last seven years for Frende as a team lead and software developer. Frende have a culture of always looking for ways to improve. This has led to strong teams, solid software and great products.
Rune now works as an international business developer for REN, where he will bring novel software for the electrical power grid to the world.
In his spare time he likes to work in his grocery garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rune-ulvnes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rune-ulvnes/</guid>
      <description>Rune is an advisor and entrepreneur, with a bachelor degree in software development and a masters degree in innovation and business development.
Rune has worked for several companies and industries, with 9 years of experience from Telenor, 3 years of experience from FINN.no and 13 years of experience from advisory for both private and government organizations.
In 2016 Rune established CoWork together with two former colleagues, a business without management inspired from the book Reinventing Organizations by Laloux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rustam-mehmandarov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/rustam-mehmandarov/</guid>
      <description>Passionate computer scientist. Java Champion ​and Google Developer Expert (GDE) ​for Cloud. Public speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/samia-touileb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/samia-touileb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/scott-hurrey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/scott-hurrey/</guid>
      <description>Scott Hurrey is a Senior Manager of a group of teams at Blackboard. In this role, he and his teams are responsible for Developer Relations, Web Property development and administration, Engineering Quality and Productivity, and the definition, relationship management, and implementation of educational standards. He has been at Blackboard for 12 years, after spending 12 years as a one-person development organization, including developer relations, in the telecom industry.
When not writing code or managing amazing teams, Scott is a snare drummer in a bagpipe band, and enjoys motorcycling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-holen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-holen/</guid>
      <description>Siv er avdelingsleder for Brukeropplevelse og design i Kantega. Hun lang erfaring som UX-lead og interaksjonsdesigner og har jobbet med digitale løsninger siden 2000. Hun er utdannet biolog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/stian-veum-m%C3%B8llersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/stian-veum-m%C3%B8llersen/</guid>
      <description>Stian er en webutvikler fra Oslo. Der jobber han med datavisualisering, interaktiv webgrafikk og digital historiefortelling for NRK. På fritida foretrekker han å fikle med språk, ord og andre former for uttrykk og undersøke hvordan de relaterer til programmering, gjerne gjennom mediumet kreativ programmering. Annen hver mandag er han og å høre i podcasten Kortslutning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/svein-erik-kro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/svein-erik-kro/</guid>
      <description>Former developer formed into QA. Loves to automate stuff. Most like to be found in a forest looking for Tupperware in trees, carrying a ladder, BigShot and climbing gear</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tatiana-kolesnikova/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tatiana-kolesnikova/</guid>
      <description>Head of Product with academic background in both IT and design, Tatiana’s main role is to organise collaboration between design, development and product parts of the team. Tatiana facilitates defining product strategy and ensures that the quality of Diggecard products meets the best world standards. When travel restriction allows, Tatiana likes to share her knowledge and experience as a speaker at design and IT conferences all over Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/therese-engen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/therese-engen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tonje-evanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tonje-evanger/</guid>
      <description>Tonje Evanger is co-founder of and CDO at Variant AS, a consultancy offering technology, design and business services.
Tonje has been in charge of design and innovation processes in both startups and large corporates for 15 years, focusing on building strategy and culture for innovation and intrapreneurship.
She is also ass. Professor of Strategic Design at NTNU, Institute of Design. She loves to learn and to share learning. Medium.com/@tonjed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tor-sporsem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/tor-sporsem/</guid>
      <description>Tor Sporsem is a researcher within software engineering and studies how developers organize and conduct their work. Software startups, communities of practice and tacit knowledge are topics recently studied. The purpose is understanding how people utilize new technology and capture this knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torkel-velure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torkel-velure/</guid>
      <description>Torkel has a masters in computer science from University of Manchester and is currently an Android developer at Shortcut Bergen. He has worked with apps for customers such as Sbanken, Rema 1000, DR, Cutters, Nordea, Pngr.. He has also been a lecturer in Android development at Kristiania, and done guest lectures at other universities.
Torkel has a not so secret hobby of code golf and competitive programming, having solved and authored thousands of coding problems on codewars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torry-tufteland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torry-tufteland/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an independent developer and consultant that enjoys building excellent stuff with peachy people. Normally .NET and React are my preferred tool belt, but I&amp;rsquo;m always open to mix it up a little.
Today the new nail gun is called react-query, and it&amp;rsquo;s a total winner! Why? Come see my talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torstein-skarra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/torstein-skarra/</guid>
      <description>Jobber nå i NAV IT, Oslo, Direktør for Design, Arkitektur, Agile Coaches og Product Managers. Har tidligere jobbet som endringskonsulent i Memetor, som konsulentsjef i Atea Larvik, Leveranseleder i Sparebank 1 Gruppen, Manager i Accenture, og vært med på flere startups innen bærekraftig mote. Tidligere presentasjoner utenom i jobb (ifm uliek roller i NAV): NASTHI-2017 Tromsø Trondheim Test Conference 2016 OdinStar (part of UKStar) Test Conference Oslo 2017 UKStar Test Conference London 2018 ODIN Test Conference Oslo 2018 TestCon Europe Test Conference (Vilnius) 2019, Vilnius UiO Forelesning om Digitalisering og transformasjon, Oslo 2021 Fra TestCon (fant ikke noen av de andre) YouTube: https://youtu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/trond-blomholm-kvamme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/trond-blomholm-kvamme/</guid>
      <description> Master degree in Computer Science from NTNU. Been developing software professionally since 2008. Experience both as a consultant and as an in-house developer. Currently leading and mentoring a group of skilled people in Kraftlauget. Passion for Git and how to work great as a team.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-haugstvedt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-haugstvedt/</guid>
      <description>Vegard is an experienced frontend developer that specializes in accessibility. His passion is making good user experiences for everyone. His currently works on getting rid of all paper applications at NAV. This is his first time in six years speaking at Booster without his toddler (now 5 years old) accompanying him, but at least his wife Cecilie is joining!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-veiset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-veiset/</guid>
      <description>Vegard is a passionate Kotlin developer and has been working with the language for the last six years. Founder of the “Pils og Programmering”-meetup in Oslo and is the practice lead for Kotlin at Bekk. When he isn&amp;rsquo;t working at his day job he spends too much time either gaming or writing his own game engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vidar-drageide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vidar-drageide/</guid>
      <description>Security stuff in Sbanken / TBA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vikas-gupta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/vikas-gupta/</guid>
      <description>Vikas Gupta is a Designer at Variant AS, a consultancy offering technology, design and business services.
He has a Master of Technology in Computer Science with specialization in Interaction Design. Vikas has worked in several exciting tech-startups as designer and frontend-developer, and with broad experience of working closely with technologists, users and stakeholders. He likes to work with and to understand people, and cares about them. Creating good and effective user experiences is important to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8ystein-ivar-malt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8ystein-ivar-malt/</guid>
      <description>Jeg er født og oppvokst i Bergen, har en mastergrad i programvareutvikling fra UiB/HVL, og har jobbet som utvikler i 6 år. Jeg er nå ansatt som konsulent i det lokale konsulentselskapet Kraftlauget, hvor jeg er utleid til TV 2s team for gravejournalistikk. Tidligere har jeg arbeidet som frontendarkitekt i Dataloy Systems, og jeg har erfaring som gjesteforeleser innen datagrafikk på HVL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8yvind-fanebust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8yvind-fanebust/</guid>
      <description>Utvikler, arkitekt og altmuligmann i Stacc. Har ca 15 års erfaring fra software-utvikling, primært innen bank og finans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8yvind-randa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%B8yvind-randa/</guid>
      <description>Technology enthusiast and Leader for Google Developer Group Bergen. Working as Solution Architect for NextGenTel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Security Architect</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/h%C3%A5kon-andr-f%C3%B8rre-knudsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/h%C3%A5kon-andr-f%C3%B8rre-knudsen/</guid>
      <description>Håkon is a developer with an above average interest in programming languages, information security and unicorns. The last few years he has been working at RamBase Cloud ERP, with a focus on getting rid of technical debt and making the product better equipped for an ever-increasing customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Associate Professor</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/felienne-hermans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/felienne-hermans/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CEO @ FotMob</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christer-nordvik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/christer-nordvik/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/einar-w-h%C3%B8st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/einar-w-h%C3%B8st/</guid>
      <description>Einar W. Høst is a computer at NRK, the Norwegian public broadcaster. He thinks that programs should be written for people to read and also for machines to laugh at. He has a PhD in Computer Science from the University of Oslo and used to be a software craftsman.
Einar blogs at https://einarwh.wordpress.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Manager</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/unni-l%C3%B8land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/unni-l%C3%B8land/</guid>
      <description>Development Manager at Tripletex. Unni has 15 years of experience from software development and has had many roles. She is a developer at heart, but have worked in managing roles the last years. She is passionate about agile and lean and how to simplify every day life for the users.
https://www.linkedin.com/in/unniloland/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frontend Developer @ Miles</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/dag-erik-l%C3%B8vgren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/dag-erik-l%C3%B8vgren/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dagerikhl/
Dag Erik hails from the southern part of Norway, and became interested in programming from an early age. Modding games started a path that would lead to a Masters Degree in Computer Science at NTNU, specializing in Interaction Design and Game Development.
His career has taken him a step from game development, and he&amp;rsquo;s currently working as an IT Consultant at Miles Bergen, where he specializes in frontend web development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fullstack Developer @ Miles</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/alexander-castillo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/alexander-castillo/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexander-castillo-72698ab9/
Alexander is currently employed as an IT consultant at Miles Bergen. He&amp;rsquo;s a dedicated fullstack developer with experience in multiple languages and frameworks, forever seeking the thrill of learning more. In the spare time he dabbles with hobby projects, music and climbing (both inside and outside).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principal Product Manager at BRYTER</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/alexandra-leisse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/alexandra-leisse/</guid>
      <description>Alexandra has more than 10 years of experience in product related roles from key Norwegian tech companies. She is currently a Principal PM at BRYTER, the leading no-code service automation platform.
Before weasling her way into tech via open source community management, Alexandra spent a decade on opera and concert stages all over Europe as a hopeful but ultimately not very successful soprano.
She blogs occasionally at https://www.troubalex.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Interaction Designer at Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-laugerud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-laugerud/</guid>
      <description>Interaction designer with a technical edge, with over 10 years experience of creating stuff to the web, with code or shapes and colors. Currently working as designsystem lead in Posten. Gamer, doodler, Lego lover and father of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Project Manager @ Media City Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ketil-moland-olsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/ketil-moland-olsen/</guid>
      <description>Ketil has 18 years of experience from the media- and media tech sectors. He is a Senior Project Manager in Media City Bergen, where he is working in the intersection between media and technology on behalf of more than a hundred member companies. In his spare time, Ketil coordinates The Things Network Community in Bergen. Being fond of all things airy, he also maintains the open source flight tracking project balena ADS-B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior R&amp;D Engineer at Nordic Semiconductor</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/markus-tacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/markus-tacker/</guid>
      <description>Markus is a coder by heart and an organizational hacker by passion. As a software crafter he uses his 20+ years of experience working as a developer, consultant, coach, mentor, and founder to build cloud-based solutions for the Internet of Things. His professional career has been greatly influenced by taking an active role in communities, whether as a participant, contributor, initiator, or speaker. He especially enjoys the diverse and deep discussion of the Software Craft Community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Software Engineer at Ardoq</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jakub-hol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/jakub-hol/</guid>
      <description>I’m a full stack Clojure(Script) developer at Ardoq, coming originally from the JVM/JS land and coding professionally since 2005. During the years I have worked on projects large and small, long and short, local and international - and I have been scarred by too much legacy code. I care deeply about productivity (and thus Clojure and DevOps) and quality and enjoy sharing my discoveries on my blog. I come from the Czech Republic but live currently in Norway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior UX Engineer at Stiftelsen SKIL</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/maja-jaakson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/maja-jaakson/</guid>
      <description>Maja is a frontend developer, UX engineer, Scrum Master, Agile Coach, and continuous improvement enthusiast. She currently works at Stiftelsen SKIL, the Norwegian Centre for Quality Improvement in Clinical Practices. During her graduate studies in Philosophy and Logic, she focused on fundamental methodological issues in logic, mathematics, analytic philosophy, and formal linguistics. That background largely influences her professional interests: she just. won&amp;rsquo;t. stop. wrestling with methodological questions about the way we work within and across teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solution Architect</title>
      <link>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/stig-nielsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.boosterconf.no/speaker/stig-nielsen/</guid>
      <description>I work at Instech (Insurance Technology Solutions AS). We create software for the marine insurance industry. I have about 20 years of experience. Been working for both startups and bigger organizations, it has been mainly finance related. Our organization&amp;rsquo;s tech stack is based on Microsoft Azure, so I have a lots of knowledge when it comes to this cloud provider. Our organization has been working in close relationship with Microsoft to develop some of our products through the Azure Fast Track program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
