<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speakers on Booster Conference 2024 Bergen</title>
    <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speakers on Booster Conference 2024 Bergen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:40:13 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/j%C3%B8rgen-kvalsvik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/j%C3%B8rgen-kvalsvik/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Utvikler&#34; - Knowit</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/lukas-schramm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/lukas-schramm/</guid>
      <description>Master i algorithms, backendutvikler i hjerte, frontendutvikler i tvang. Nybergenser som ønsker å lære seg bergensk geografi og derfor lagte et forferdelig spill om Bergen. En av få mennesker på planeten som synes at Bergensk er pent. Overbevist oslokritiker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advisor at NAV</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/einar-h%C3%B8st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/einar-h%C3%B8st/</guid>
      <description>Einar W. Høst has been a software developer for a long time. He is working as a socio-technical advisor at the Norwegian Labour and Welfare Administration. He enjoys collaborative modelling, API design and computer programming. Over the past ten years, he has done talks on a variety of topics, including hypermedia, resiliency, recursive art and lambda calculus. He has a PhD in Computer Science from the University of Oslo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile Lead at Sparebanken Vest</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/iryna-vasylenko/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/iryna-vasylenko/</guid>
      <description>I have been working around 20 years in IT, currently as Agile Lead and Tester in Sparebanken Vest. I have passion for quality issuance, automation, and team processes. I am from beautiful Ukraine, where I studied and started my career path: developer, QA and team lead. Since that I have been working in few companies in Norway, both with international and local teams. I like to say that each developer is different, I like to learn their preferable way of working and find the best way of collaborating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alliander</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/daan-van-berkel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/daan-van-berkel/</guid>
      <description>Daan van Berkel is a enthusiastic software tinkerer with a knack for presenting technical details in a clear and concise manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Security Architect</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/h%C3%A5kon-knudsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/h%C3%A5kon-knudsen/</guid>
      <description>Håkon is a developer with an above average interest in programming languages, information security and unicorns. Their biggest passion is authentication and authorization, which has lead them to work on exciting projects such as HelseID, a national trust service for the Norwegian health sector, built on OAuth and OpenID Connect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS, Senior Solutions Architect</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/yves-hwang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/yves-hwang/</guid>
      <description>Currently thinking big, inventing and simplifying for my customers as a Senior Solutions Architect in AWS. I am a co-founder of wanda.space and a software engineer at heart. Building products is my craft as is my passion for creating a team culture that is innovative, inclusive, diverse, and based on a growth mindset that loves learning and seeks to solve challenging problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking mass mailings and data exports since 1983</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/b%C3%A5rd-aase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/b%C3%A5rd-aase/</guid>
      <description>Bård Aase has 20 years of experience as a developer and is currently a DevOps specialist in the platform team at Sbanken - et konsept fra DNB. He is committed to quality in every step throughout the software lifecycle. Bård is an avid supporter of open source and has been an active member of the Bergen Linux User Group, where he has organized lectures and meetings for many years. github.com/elzapp | mastodon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capra Consulting AS, Chief People Officer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/heidi-brovold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/heidi-brovold/</guid>
      <description>Heidi er informatiker, teknologileder og &amp;ldquo;design tenker&amp;rdquo;. Læring er forutsetningen for all utvikling. Derfor leter Heidi etter læring i alle kroker. Hun har vært utvikler, forskningsleder, prosjekt- og programleder og CTO. Nå er hun CP(eople)O i Capra Consulting AS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDO - Variant Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-s%C3%A6tersdal-hartveit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-s%C3%A6tersdal-hartveit/</guid>
      <description>I am a technology-interested designer with a primary area of expertise in UX/UI design and digital product design. As CDO at Variant in Bergen, I help my clients to design products that bring value to their users and their organisation.
In addition to my passion for design, I am also interested in team culture and interdisciplinary collaboration, especially between designers and developers.
Outside work I like to enjoy food and drinks, especially craft beer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief People Officer @ Variant</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marius-krakeli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marius-krakeli/</guid>
      <description>Marius is an ex programmer now turned product manager with a fondness for fantastic product experiences. Although spending most of his time thinking about product development, he also maintains his programming skills by being both producer and panelist on the JavaScript podcast “BartJS Podcast”. When he’s not working as a consultant at Variant, he is very entertained by video games and audio production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Process and Innovation Officer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristin-wulff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristin-wulff/</guid>
      <description>Kristin has a master in psychology (1996) and a master in organization and management (2014). She is now employed as the Chief process and innovation officer (CPIO) in Kantega and has recently finished a PhD degree at the Norwegian University of Science and Technology, Faculty of Economics and Management. She has worked within software development in different roles since 1998, the last 15 years in leadership positions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud and platform at ScaleAQ</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-olsen-gulla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-olsen-gulla/</guid>
      <description>Very interested in all things cloud, platform, containers, architecture, iot, etc..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Native practice lead in Bekk</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ole-kristian-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ole-kristian-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Developer/senior consultant and cloud native practice lead in Bekk. Interested in cloud architectures, CI/CD and developer productivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultant @ Bouvet</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/embla-%C3%B8ye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/embla-%C3%B8ye/</guid>
      <description>Embla jobber som fullstack utvikler, og er utdannet sivilingeniør i havbruk fra UiB. Hun har 2 års erfaring fra konsulentlivet og jobber for tiden i Bouvet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultant at Savvy</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ole-eskild-steensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ole-eskild-steensen/</guid>
      <description>Ole is working as a consultant at Savvy. Most of his career he has worked as a software developer for companies that has names starting with &amp;ldquo;Fjord&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultant, Bouvet</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/daria-krasnianska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/daria-krasnianska/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a certified agile team coach and project manager with 13 years of experience in IT. Also, I&amp;rsquo;m a founder and board director of a volunteer organisation. My biggest passion is people and their interactions, which makes me believe that mastering people skills is the way to survive in today&amp;rsquo;s world. I prefer a challenging but supportive approach when leading projects and teams. I tend to create an environment where colleagues can leverage their personal and professional potential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craftsman at Kraftlauget</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/oddmar-sandvik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/oddmar-sandvik/</guid>
      <description>Oddmar is an experienced architect, developer and adviser with 30 years&amp;rsquo; experience helping clients solve complex system challenges.
He is currently hired by DNB Markets to assist their journey to modernize and migrate their systems to public clouds.
Oddmar is also quite lazy and likes tools that do the work for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTO at Lyll and developer at Nicode</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/nicolai-gjellestad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/nicolai-gjellestad/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m mainly a back-end developer with experience in Go and C#, but I delve into exploring other technologies and languages as well. I have experience as a project manager and tech lead, I care about making people and teams do great stuff while having a good time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datajournalist, NRK</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/hannah-hansen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/hannah-hansen/</guid>
      <description>Hannah jobber som datajournalist for NRKs undersøkende redaksjon på Vestlandet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer and frontend developer at Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/maiken-beate-fjellanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/maiken-beate-fjellanger/</guid>
      <description>Maiken is a frontend developer and designer with love for usability and accessible design. On her most recent project she contributed to implementation of WCAG 2.1 and Tilgjengelighetserklæring at Fiskeridirektoratet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer i Variant</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sofie-thornhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sofie-thornhill/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designpotet i Liflig</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-landro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-landro/</guid>
      <description>Anne har tro på at en liten dråpe kan skape ringvirkninger i et stort hav, at summen av de små detaljene utgjør forskjellen og at verden blir et bedre sted hvis vi ser mennesket bak masken.
Anne jobber med å videreutvikle Liflig - et selskap som tar totalansvar for å skreddersy IT-drømmer. Her tilfører hun designtankegang i alle kriker og kroker av selskapet.
Liflig er et selskap i Capra-gruppen, en gruppe av selskaper med samme hjerte.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer @ Amedia</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elisabeth-irgens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elisabeth-irgens/</guid>
      <description>Elisabeth attended a CSS course back in 2006, and has been writing code for a living ever since. She still doesn’t fit the industry mold for a frontend developer, and has by now revolted against any notion that standardized skill sets are beneficial to the team sport of software development anyway. Today she’s having a blast at Amedia Produkt og Teknologi, wrangling Node.js apps that make up the micro-frontend architecture for 100+ local editorial media sites from around Norway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer @ Knowit</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/guro-prestegard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/guro-prestegard/</guid>
      <description>Developer @ Knowit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer @ Storebrand</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/janniche-lange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/janniche-lange/</guid>
      <description>Developer @ Storebrand. I like pair programming and delivering value to customers. Care about testing, readable code and frequent deliveries. And naming things. Also people and interactions more than processes and tools. And agile. Involved in communities for knowledge sharing; javaBin, Stavanger Agile Meetup and the new software conference HelloStavanger.no</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Apparat</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christine-smith-johnsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christine-smith-johnsen/</guid>
      <description>Developer at Apparat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Apparat</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elisabeth-whiteley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elisabeth-whiteley/</guid>
      <description>.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Bouvet</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/erik-andreas-r%C3%B8kland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/erik-andreas-r%C3%B8kland/</guid>
      <description>Erik Andreas is a passionate developer at Bouvet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Elmera</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%A5dne-forslund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%A5dne-forslund/</guid>
      <description>System developer from Trøndelag, with experience from the design industry, forklift driving, big consulting and now in-house developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Kraftlauget AS</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/amar-topalovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/amar-topalovic/</guid>
      <description>Amar has a masters degree in Computer Science from the University of Copenhagen, specializing in parallel programming and algorithms. During his studies he worked as a student developer at IBM. Today he works as a consultant at Kraftlauget, where he works with backend web development, mostly in .NET. He is particularly interested in functional and high-performance (GPU) programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Kraftlauget AS</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/syver-storm-furru/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/syver-storm-furru/</guid>
      <description>I am a frontend developer at Kraftlauget AS, who sometimes dabbles in the tech lead role. I like old and/or strange programming languages, food and wine, board games, and the occational hike with my dog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Oslo Origo</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marit-%C3%A5nestad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marit-%C3%A5nestad/</guid>
      <description>Marit har 11 års erfaring som utvikler og har et sterkt engasjement for å lage gode og samfunnsnyttige løsninger. Stortrives i tverrfaglige miljøer der hun kan bidra på mange forskjellige måter for å sikre et solid sluttprodukt.
Jobber nå hos Oslo Origo, digitaliseringsetaten i Oslo kommune</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer at Variant Trondheim</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/jakob-endrestad-kielland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/jakob-endrestad-kielland/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Jakob! 👋
I work as a developer and consultant for Variant Trondheim and I&amp;rsquo;m a life-long computer nerd. Day-to-day I spend most of my time working frontend with a great group of people (my team), but I love diving into other parts of the stack from time to time, such as our deployment pipelines. Besides technology my biggest passion is teaching. I worked as a part-time private teacher throughout all my years as a student, and I love the challenge of communicating something difficult in an interesting and understandable way, something that will hopefully shine through in my talk!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer in TV 2</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/astrid-johnsen-tessem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/astrid-johnsen-tessem/</guid>
      <description>Astrid Tessem works as a backend developer in TV 2. Her main focus is to improve the user experience on TV 2 Play by creating a more personalized experience. She has also 4 years experience as a data scientist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer on the AI team at Helse Vest IKT</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/johanna-j%C3%B8sang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/johanna-j%C3%B8sang/</guid>
      <description>Johanna is a data scientist and developer at Helse Vest IKT. She holds a bachelors in cognitive science and a masters in machine learning, both from UiB. Professionally she has worked on projects involving computer vision and natural language processing. She enjoys discussing the future of AI and speculate on the impact it will have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer, team lead and mentor</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-midtun-hollup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-midtun-hollup/</guid>
      <description>Siv loves creating software, preferably together with other people. She works both as a developer and a team lead. A strong passion for teaching and outreach led her to help found the Nerdschool meetup and teach fundamental software engineering skills at the University of Bergen. She is still actively engaged in teaching newcomers to our field about craftsmanship of developing software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director of Software Engineering (CTO) at Avanade</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anders-nor%C3%A5s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anders-nor%C3%A5s/</guid>
      <description>Originally educated in arts and design, Anders has spent the last twenty years writing code.
He has given numerous talks and keynotes at conferences such as JavaZone, NDC, J-Fall, Øredev and many more. Have given 100+ conference talks to a variety of audiences including media, design and hardcore computer science. Known for an energetic and highly engaging presentations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director of Technology at Knowit Experience Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andr-heie-vik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andr-heie-vik/</guid>
      <description>André is the Director of Technology at Knowit Experience Bergen. He is an enthusiastic and experienced technology leader and agilist with a strong background in software development. Before moving to a management role, he spent more than a decade as a software developer. André was part of the team establishing the Booster conference and helped organize the conference from 2011-2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Driven Design Coach at CoWork, Norway</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/mufrid-krilic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/mufrid-krilic/</guid>
      <description>Mufrid is devoted to leading and coaching product development teams, by cultivating knowledge sharing in the organization and increasing co-developer’s business understanding. His professional philosophy is rooted in Domain-Driven Design and in building agile and technical coaching culture on an organization-wide level. With 20+ years of experience as software architect, developer and technical coach, Mufrid has been deeply involved in developing enterprise-solutions in complex domains, such as healthcare, insurance and telecom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer &amp; Security Champion at Kantega SSO</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elias-brattli-s%C3%B8rensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elias-brattli-s%C3%B8rensen/</guid>
      <description>Software Engineer &amp;amp; Security Champion at Kantega SSO, engineering digital identity standards for secure authentication to the Atlassian ecosystem while facilitating and promoting secure software development practices. Passionate about software security, and is coordinating the Kantega subject group for Security by Design.
M. Sc. in Computer Science at NTNU, where he was researching usage of static analysis tools like Spotbugs to find vulnerabilities in OpenID Connect client implementations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fostering Team Spirit in the World of Tech at Webstep</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/cathrine-fredh%C3%B8i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/cathrine-fredh%C3%B8i/</guid>
      <description>After many years of studying psychology in London, so far as to get a doctorate in the field, Cathrine decided to move back to Norway and cultivate her interest in technology. In Webstep, she stands as an arbiter, managing consultants and the vast spectrum of tech services they provide for their clients. Cathrine has always shown to have a keen interest in team harmony and productivity, while always staying on top of developments at the crossroads of tech and psychology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front End Developer @ Variant</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristoffer-nordstr-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/kristoffer-nordstr-m/</guid>
      <description>Kristoffer has a big heart for humanity &amp;amp; inclusion. He has been working with GUIs since the 1990s, a &amp;ldquo;Nordic citizen&amp;rdquo; from Sweden with Finnish roots living in Oslo Norway. Previous Head of Front End at the Norwegian Red Cross and currently working as a Consultant at Variant building education systems of the future for Sikt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front-end developer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/catriona-mackenzie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/catriona-mackenzie/</guid>
      <description>Originally hailing from London, Catriona left the high-pressure world of financial IT in 2012 to enjoy a more relaxed pace of life in the beautiful, mountainous city of Bergen, Norway, where she took up a new career as a web developer. Since then she has worked with various back-end web technologies before finally landing her dream role as front-end developer, and now spends most of her days wrestling with CSS in an attempt to turn designers’ wishes into reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontend developer and accessibility advocate at Webstep</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-haugstvedt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-haugstvedt/</guid>
      <description>An enthusiastic accessibility advocate, always preaching about WCAG, WAI-ARIA, A11Y and other abbreviations. Has red-green color vision deficiency and recognize situations in everyday life where we all benefit from accessible services.
As a frontend developer, Vegard enjoys working on the &amp;ldquo;front of frontend&amp;rdquo;, in the intersection between programming and UX, and his goal is that the services he works on should be accessible to everyone, regardless of their preferred platform or their abilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontend lead</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/stian-morsund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/stian-morsund/</guid>
      <description>Stian Morsund has a computer engineering degree from HVL. He is now frontend-lead at KS Digitale Fellestjenester after being a consultant for some years. He has previously talked at various events like JavaZone and JavaBin here in Bergen. Likes gamedevelopment, cats and contributing to opensource projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontend-consultant</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/malin-jakobsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/malin-jakobsen/</guid>
      <description>Frontend utvikler som jobber for Miles i Bergen, med stor interesse for brukerdesign og accessibility</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fullstack developer at Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-valen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/martin-valen/</guid>
      <description>Martin is a fullstack developer who never really thought about accessibility and therefore has several inaccessible pages on his conscience. He wanted to fix that problem, but didn&amp;rsquo;t find a proper introduction to accessibilty, so he went together with Maiken and made one!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of Website and Mobile App at Widerøe</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/tore-stensaker-tefre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/tore-stensaker-tefre/</guid>
      <description>Tore is the current Head of Website and Mobile App at Widerøe, a Norwegian regional airline having Bergen as one of their focus cities.
Formerly, Tore was a consultant at Variant, where he developed and released a number of mobility and public transport apps and web solutions throughout Norway.
Before starting at Variant, Tore graduated from NTNU in Trondheim, with an MSc in Informatics in 2021. Tore have previously also worked as a software developer intern at Oslo Børs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Centered Designer, Equinor</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-lise-bergem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anne-lise-bergem/</guid>
      <description>20 years experience as a Product designer. I work as a Human Centred Designer at Equinor. For the past 12 years I have been designing digital products and services for clients in a range of industries; financial, energy, health, education, media and games. I have had roles like lead designer, service designer &amp;amp; UX/UI designer. My education is a MS in Industrial Design from the Oslo School of Architecture, the Norwegian Entrepreneurship School, and I have an Executive Master in Strategic Design for Innovation - Design Thinking from NHH/HVL/UIB.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indeed, QA Automation Engineer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/mesut-durukal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/mesut-durukal/</guid>
      <description>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1lKTxhk1KEhXBw4kJRTBnHrfusn1S6-Yi/view?usp=share_link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT consultant, Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/even-ask-sleire/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/even-ask-sleire/</guid>
      <description>Even has been working as an IT consultant at Kantega for 1.5 years, with a primary focus on backend development. He also finds enjoyment in contributing to the frontend side of applications.
He has a strong affinity for simplicity in code, believing that clean and straightforward solutions contribute to better maintainability and understanding of software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT-Architect at DNB Markets</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>For the past 13 years, Christian has been working as a developer and architect for DNB Markets, operating and contributing to an array of different solutions, technologies and platforms. He has a keen interest for tool smithing and pipelines. Building useful tools and services to streamline, simplify and improve daily work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurist og teknolog</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/julie-eld%C3%B8y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/julie-eld%C3%B8y/</guid>
      <description>Julie er konsulent i Capra Consulting. Hun jobber mest som agile coach og teamleder. Med en tverrfaglig bakgrunn fra både juss og teknologi, trives hun spesielt godt i det skjæringspunktet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kantega AS</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie-daae-nilsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/cecilie-daae-nilsen/</guid>
      <description>Backend utvikler</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kantega AS</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/j%C3%B8rgen-langemyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/j%C3%B8rgen-langemyr/</guid>
      <description>Jørgen er en utvikler fra Kantega</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making interactive frontends for NRKs audience</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-kjelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/morten-kjelling/</guid>
      <description>Morten is a developer with a passion for user experience, performance, accessibility and design. For the last 2 years he has been building live TV interactions in NRK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing consultant at Itera</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/dalibor-jovic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/dalibor-jovic/</guid>
      <description>Dalibor worked on over 200 projects in last 18 years. In Itera Dalibor works as a tech lead and a full-stack developer. He is also practice lead for AI-tools in Itera, making sure that all employees and customers get the most out of available AI tools. In his free time he makes videos about AI on LinkedIn, and videos about programming on YouTube. Advocate for clean code, and improving efficiency in all areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metodeansvarlig, Team-as-a-Service, Webstep</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/fredrik-anthonisen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/fredrik-anthonisen/</guid>
      <description>Fredrik, metodeansvarlig for Team-as-a-Service i Webstep, har ledet utviklingen av selskapets rammeverk for teametablering. Med en bakgrunn som spenner fra utvikling til prosjekt- og teknologiledelse, er han godt kjent med utfordringene i både små og store bedrifter. Hans arbeidsmåte er farget av systemtenking og et smidig tankesett. I hans reise gjennom komplekse prosjekter, blir ærlighet, nysgjerrighet, og åpenhet naturlige ledetråder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles, Developer IT-Security</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/brynjar-steinbakk-ulriksen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/brynjar-steinbakk-ulriksen/</guid>
      <description>Brynjar is a full-stack developer with an interest in Azure, DevOps, security, and integration. He has worked on security solutions at Equinor and currently is a part of the security team at Sbanken. In his free time, he has won two coding competitions in Stavanger, achieved the Azure DevOps expert certification, and played an active role in various roles in sports, stock analysis, and organization and management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nå personalleder i NAV IT, tidligere konsulent i 12 år</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ingeborg-klungland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ingeborg-klungland/</guid>
      <description>Ingeborg har jobbet 12 år som konsulent i Capra Consulting AS, nesten alltid med å lede prosjekter og team mot et eller annet. Hun er stadig fascinert av hvordan mellommenneskelige forhold har et stort potensiale for å både øke og senke fart og flyt, mer enn det tekniske forhold ofte har. Det har gitt Ingeborg masse inspirasjon til å jobbe med teamdynamikk og hvordan få teamene hun jobber med til å jobbe best mulig sammen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platformutvikler SPV</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-thuen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/andreas-thuen/</guid>
      <description>Jobbmer med å drifte og videreutvikle skypaltformen til Sparebanken Vest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Consultant at Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ove-gram-nipen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ove-gram-nipen/</guid>
      <description>Ove is a full-stack developer with 20 years of experience. In his spare time he goes sailing with his wife and two kids, and practices Taekwon-Do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Lead, Mendix</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elizabeth-zagroba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elizabeth-zagroba/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth is Quality Lead at Mendix in The Netherlands. She discovers and fills in the gaps in exploratory testing by coordinating an ensemble (mob) testing practice, actively listening, and setting out to prove that when “it should just work” it actually does. She&amp;rsquo;s the go-to person for thinking critically about what’s being built, creating a common understanding, supporting colleagues outside the prescribed management structure, and writing API tests and English effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schibsted, Engineering Manager</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/birgir-stefansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/birgir-stefansson/</guid>
      <description>TBW</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Consultant, Miles</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/julian-philipp-merlin-ertel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/julian-philipp-merlin-ertel/</guid>
      <description>Julian works as a senior consultant for Miles Bergen. His main competence is C++ development, but over the years he has gathered experience in a variety of different languages and technologies. As a developer he has mainly worked in the domains of video processing and seismic data acquisition. When given the option Julian&amp;rsquo;s language of choice is Rust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior designer &amp; advisor at Haltenbanken</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%A5sta-lindemann/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/%C3%A5sta-lindemann/</guid>
      <description>Åsta is a senior designer from the brand design agency Haltenbanken in Bergen. She has a master in design, further education in Strategic design for innovation - Design Thinking, and has also completes «AI and Design Thinking», a part of the Technology Management and Digital Transformation master programme at NTNU. Åsta has extensive experience in strategic design development through the use of design methodology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior frontend developer, Kantega Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-grimsgaard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/christian-grimsgaard/</guid>
      <description>Christian is a senior frontend developer at Kantega, and is highly enthusiastic about pixels and coffee. Ask him about React or the optimal way to roast a washed Kenyan coffee, and he’ll talk for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Frontendutvikler - Sopra Steria</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sebastian-fr%C3%B8yen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sebastian-fr%C3%B8yen/</guid>
      <description>Sebastian jobber hos Sopra Steria som en frontendutvikler der han arbeider med React. På fritiden så pumper han jern eller spiller Baldur’s gate 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Security Consultant @ Atea</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/joakim-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/joakim-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>Joakim is a senior security consultant at Atea and works with penetration testing and incident response. He is passionate about security and contiously looks for ways to enhance the collaboration between the red and blue teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Test Engineer at the Dutch Electoral Council</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/joep-schuurkes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/joep-schuurkes/</guid>
      <description>Joep wandered into software testing in 2006. After a decade of both exploratory testing and test automation, his focus shifted to a bigger question. How can teams and organizations build and deliver good software? To answer that question, he has been exploring topics such as technical leadership, quality engineering, and software methodologies.
Joep has given talks and workshops at conferences throughout Europe. He&amp;rsquo;s also one of the organizers of the Friends of Good Software unconference (FroGS conf).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior visuell og UX-designer i Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/helene-storstr%C3%B8m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/helene-storstr%C3%B8m/</guid>
      <description>Helene er designer hos Kantega i Oslo og jobber for tiden med Posten sin app. Hun er utdannet designer med både bachelorgrad og fagbrev, i tillegg har hun også et år med læringspsykologi i bagasjen. Dette gir henne et unikt perspektiv som designer. For med dette kan hun kombinere atferd, design og teknologi når hun jobber med løsninger for å finne ut hva som er best for brukeren. Etter jobb finner du henne ofte ute på treninger med hunden, som hun også konkurrerer aktivt med.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior-konsulent hos Webstep</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/hege-liby-erdal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/hege-liby-erdal/</guid>
      <description>Hege has a PhD in experiment nuclear physics, and is now working as a senior backend developer in Webstep. For the past 3 years she has been a part of the team at KS Digitale fellestjenester.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seniorkonsulent og medeier hos Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/brage-breivik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/brage-breivik/</guid>
      <description>Brage er den på laget som aldri klarer å holde seg i posisjon men virrer over hele banen, men som likevel bidrar til et godt resultat. UX, frontend, backend - alt er gøy og må prøves, noen ganger med godt resultat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senoir Consultant, Tech Lead</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricki-sickenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ricki-sickenger/</guid>
      <description>Programmer, gamer, father of three kids. Games, Backend, Frontend, AR/VR and IT Consultant. Also a hobby game developer and retro computer enthusiast. =)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/abel-van-beek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/abel-van-beek/</guid>
      <description>Abel van Beek is a software developer with a passion for front-end magic and creating kick-ass user experiences. It is not only about software either: he is about making it accessible for everyone, inclusive, and a force for good. His Dutch roots show not just in his love for chocolate sprinkles, but also in his pragmatic approach to complex issues.
At Vizrt, he tightly integrated their design system workflow with the LEGO blocks he created to quickly build and maintain accessible web applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Developer at Equinor</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anna-kvashchuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anna-kvashchuk/</guid>
      <description>Anna Kvashchuk is a software developer at Equinor, mom to 1- and 5-year-old, wife to mathematician, and someone who prefers family retrospective to couples&amp;rsquo; therapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer @Instech</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/eugene-rebedailo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/eugene-rebedailo/</guid>
      <description>Eugene is a software engineer at Instech, a company specializing in software for the marine insurance industry. He has fascination with game design, data modelling and Sichuan cuisine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solution Architect Instech Solutions</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/stig-nielsen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/stig-nielsen/</guid>
      <description>I am a solution architect and tech lead at Instech (Insurance Technology Solutions AS). We create software for the marine insurance industry. I have about 20 years of experience. Been working for both startups and bigger organizations, it has been mainly finance related. Our tech stack is Microsoft/Azure based. When it comes to presenting, I have done several sessions/talks internally within the company on a wide range of topics. I did lightning talks at booster 2022 (MDM Pattern) and 2023 (Internal tech talks).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storebrand, Offensive Security Manager</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/oleksandr-kazymyrov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/oleksandr-kazymyrov/</guid>
      <description>Oleksandr is an experienced cybersecurity professional with a passion for offensive security. He has led numerous engagements across a variety of industries, helping clients identify and address critical security vulnerabilities in their systems and infrastructure. As an Offensive Security Manager at Storebrand, Oleksandr has also been responsible for growing and managing a red team program, which has helped Storebrand enhance its security posture and better understand its risks and vulnerabilities. With a background in software engineering and a deep understanding of offensive tactics, he is uniquely positioned to help organizations adopt modern and effective offensive security practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tagline</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anette-bergo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/anette-bergo/</guid>
      <description>biography</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Lead</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marit-hellest%C3%B8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marit-hellest%C3%B8/</guid>
      <description>Im Marit I currently work as a Team leader/Developer at Casi AS. This is my first inhouse experience as I´ve been a consultant for the last 8 years, having touched upon most types of development, from large backend projects, small websites, app development and so on.
The most fun part of the job is to challenge myself and learn new things, preferrably outside my comfort zone, which is also why I&amp;rsquo;m trying my hand at holding a talk at a conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Lead in Cubit AS</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/frida-sulen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/frida-sulen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Lead at Instech </title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ami-ahalpara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ami-ahalpara/</guid>
      <description>Ami finds great joy in creating software and has lately been enjoying learning and practicing all things related to tech leadership. As a Tech Lead and Developer at Instech, she enjoys enabling her team in solving business problems, applying agile principles and continuously delivering value to customers. She likes to be a part of architectural and design decisions, removing any roadblocks, and helping foster psychological safety and collaborative culture within the team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech lead NRK.no</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ingrid-guren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/ingrid-guren/</guid>
      <description>Ingrid is tech lead for JavaScript at NRK.no and has performed a disaster recovery of the front page at three in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech lead NRK.no</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/john-arne-s-pedersen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/john-arne-s-pedersen/</guid>
      <description>John Arne is the tech lead for Java at NRK.no, and he was on duty when Eurovision Song Contest Norwegian national final crashed in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tietoevry, Senior Consulent</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/yijun-pan-stautland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/yijun-pan-stautland/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer and consultant at Tietoevry in Bergen. My passion for technology sparked with my very first PC and has grown ever since. Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve dedicated myself to mastering best practices and theories in various programming disciplines. My enthusiasm for Git has made me the go-to guy in our company. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my insights and learnings as I make my debut at the Booster conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User experience designer by education, full stack developer by trade.</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/nils-norman-hauk%C3%A5s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/nils-norman-hauk%C3%A5s/</guid>
      <description>Hi!
I lead a one-person technology studio named Builder Heart where I dream up, and make programs for people. Also, I like to blog and share my findings with others.
Currently dabbling in running my own infrastructure using Ansible, learning Linux system administration, and deploying Common Lisp (or Clojure) in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ux designer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/erika-h%C3%A5gensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/erika-h%C3%A5gensen/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an empathatic, curious and positive designer. I have worked as a desiger for both startups as well as large banks.
I&amp;rsquo;m also an experienced circus artist!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Designer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/helene-sofie-stenstadvold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/helene-sofie-stenstadvold/</guid>
      <description>Passionate about creating great user experiences within the Fintech space. Currently working as a UX Designer at Stacc Oslo, but have previously worked at Tryg and Sparebanken Vest in Bergen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Designer at Variant Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sindre-holm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/sindre-holm/</guid>
      <description>Senior UX designer hos Variant Bergen. Bakgrunn som designer i Anti Bergen og Schibsted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Designer at Variant Bergen</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-feste/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegard-feste/</guid>
      <description>UX Designer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Engineer, EDS core team, Equinor</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/maja-maria-dawn-jaakson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/maja-maria-dawn-jaakson/</guid>
      <description>Maja has an academic background in philosophy, linguistics and logic and a professional background in web dev and agile coaching. She had the pleasure and good fortune of joining the Equinor Design System (EDS) Core Team in 2023 as a UX Engineer. Professionally speaking, she’s into stuff at the intersection of dev and design and all things process, collaboration and quality improvement. She is also one of the organizers of the Frontiers Bergen meetup group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Manager in Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-holen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/siv-holen/</guid>
      <description>Siv is a senior interaction designer and has worked with digital user experiences for over 20 years. She is excited about new ways of working with UX in the era of AI. She has recently taken the couse &amp;ldquo;AI and design thinking&amp;rdquo; at NTNU and wants to share her experiences with you. Siv is a manager for User Experience and Design in Kantega.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Strategist and Design Researcher</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/becca-kennedy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/becca-kennedy/</guid>
      <description>Becca is an independent UX consultant in Albany, New York, USA with a PhD in Psychology. She loves working with teams on thoughtful and impactful products and services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX-designer i Kantega</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elen-haks%C3%B8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/elen-haks%C3%B8/</guid>
      <description>Elen er UX-designer hos Kantega i Oslo, og jobber for tiden med bedriftsnettbanken Sparebank 1. Hun har en Master i Interaksjonsdesign fra Norges teknisk-naturvitenskapelige universitet, og Bachelor i Mediedesign fra Høyskolen i Volda og Griffith University. Hun har også studert UX Design hos Noroff. Etter jobb finner du henne ofte med kamera i hånda, eller på tur i skogen med hunden Ted og hesten Rosie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marie-stoltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/marie-stoltz/</guid>
      <description>Marie forsøkte seg i C++ på slutten av 90-tallet, men tok en u-sving og har siden da pådratt seg over 20 års erfaring innen ulike typer digitaliseringsprosjekter. Marie har ledet designavdelinger og tverrfaglige team, og hun har sett mange ulike typer produktteam, avdelinger og organisasjoner fra innsiden. Marie brenner for innovasjon og endring gjennom å forstå andre mennesker. Hun er også daglig leder for Variant i Bergen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web designer</title>
      <link>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegar-norman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2024.boosterconf.no/speaker/vegar-norman/</guid>
      <description>I am a web designer who enjoys working somewhere inbetween design and code, mostly with large-scale web portals and design systems. I love working with accessibility and challenges that involves the end user, and how we as developers can make the web a better place for everyone. I spend my free time as a moderator in Norsk programmering, the largest Discord server for Norwegian coders, and focus my efforts around creating a community that is open and welcoming to everyone, no matter the skill level or ambition.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
